<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sarpa hara ☾</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on sarpa hara ☾</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 06:00:35 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Psychiatry</title>
      <link>/psychiatry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 06:00:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/psychiatry/</guid>
      <description>Only psychiatrists will ask you if you want to go from dose X to dose Y of some given drug. Who should be doing the asking? If years of medical school are doing the asking, something is wrong.
Only psychiatrists will chastise you for giving the “wrong” response, because they weren’t asking you, they were giving you the illusion of free will by offering the opportunity to show alignment with their opinion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viloxazine</title>
      <link>/viloxazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 23:53:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/viloxazine/</guid>
      <description>Recently I posted a picture of a “connoisseur kit” featuring this re-branded Viloxazine formulation, the new Irresponsible Mother’s Little Helper, “Totally Not Speed” for belligerent children who won’t stay seated in their damn chairs, or whatever.
Viloxazine is an old antidepressant with a complex pharmacology (NRI / 5-H2B antag / 5-HT2C ag / 5-HT7 antag).
The posted picture garnered some attention, specifically from a handful of my ADHD co-diagnosees, who started screaming at me about the benefits of medicating very young children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strolling Through Hypnagogic Hyperspace</title>
      <link>/gabo-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 19:11:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gabo-2/</guid>
      <description>Gaboxadol is a structural derivative of the alkaloid Muscimol, a constituent of the pharmacological cocktail in the Amanita muscaria species of mushroom. A powerful, yet non-reinforcing hypnotic agent (unlike benzodiazepines, which are often prescribed for insomnia), Gaboxadol never found its way into any pharmaceutical production line for a constellation of complex reasons.
In my previous report, I wrote that Gaboxadol is &amp;ldquo;beyond powerful&amp;rdquo;. That assertion has been reinforced numerous times during a month-long gradual (upward) dose titration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Parroting the Soundbites of Anti-Drug Propaganda</title>
      <link>/propaganda/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 19:11:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/propaganda/</guid>
      <description>I believe that the drug enthusiast community is becoming increasingly better at striking a behavioral balance between normalizing sustainable and responsible drug-fueled hedonism and making the idea of harm reduction salient.
Most of us have been exposed to biased, moralistic anti-drug propaganda. Some of us (rightfully so) aim to deconstruct such propaganda and invalidate it as a reductionist, uninformed viral idea about a specific drug (“GHB is a date-rape drug.&amp;quot;) or a category of substances (“All opioids are morbidly addictive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mirogabalin [Besylate]</title>
      <link>/mirogabalin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 19:07:37 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mirogabalin/</guid>
      <description>Gabapentinoids are the Vegemite™ of pharmaceuticals: it&amp;rsquo;s all love or hate, and almost never in between. If you clicked on this post, you are probably familiar with the fuzzy, electrifying stimulation brought about by an unholy dose of Pregabalin, or the fickle GHB-like lust from scarfing down Phenibut by the tablespoon, or the hassle of leaving CVS with bucket-sized refills of Gabapentin – the original gangsta Gabapentinoid.
I had assumed that my own first-hand familiarity with the &amp;lsquo;Noids made me well-equipped for my future acquaintance with Tarlige™ (Mirogabalin Besylate).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyclazodone</title>
      <link>/cyclazodone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 12:38:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cyclazodone/</guid>
      <description>Have you heard about the new kid on the block? If you frequent r/researchchemicals, you might have.
The kid is not so new. In the late 60s and early 70s, pharmaceutical amphetamine abuse in the United States was hiking up a steep hill. The Benzedrine Era was nearing its end, making way for everyone&amp;rsquo;s favorite Controlled Substances Act of 1971. For pharmaceutical manufacturers, it was research o&amp;rsquo;clock. The stimulant market wasn&amp;rsquo;t becoming any less lucrative, even with tighter regulations now in place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phendimetrazine [Tartrate]</title>
      <link>/phendimetrazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 03:18:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/phendimetrazine/</guid>
      <description>I’ve had the fortune of running the stimulant gamut, from Adderall to Desoxyn. Going into this experience, I had some comparisons to draw. The literature on this compound was intriguing, but In my skeptical expectations there were no foreseeable surprises. It’s another stimulant, what’s the big dealio? Golly gee I was mistaken.
Didn’t even walk 50 feet from the pharmacy before popping one because I’m an impatient and excitable SOB. Walking to the subway on a chilly northeastern evening, I was hoping the 35mg of obscure stim goodness would warm me up a little.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gaboxadol [Hydrochloride]</title>
      <link>/gaboxadol/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 23:53:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gaboxadol/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: I can&amp;rsquo;t and don&amp;rsquo;t recommend Gaboxadol to anyone because it is a narrowly studied substance, and everything I say is just my opinion and not medical advice.
Tonight we&amp;rsquo;re packing 20mg of Gaboxadol HCl in a gelatin cap in hopes of getting some stellar sleep, or I don&amp;rsquo;t know, a couple&#39; rotating cubes or whatever.
I&amp;rsquo;m cheating a little because this is technically my 2nd trial. The 1st &amp;ldquo;allergy&amp;rdquo; trial was done with 10mg down the hatch, about a week ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Metaphor for Life and Fun</title>
      <link>/metaphor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 15:00:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/metaphor/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Just have fun and enjoy life.&amp;rdquo;
Imagine that you have set out to discover a new continent. All the years behind you were spent dreaming of this achievement. Likely, you would be crossing vast bodies of water and weathering numerous storms. This journey is, expectedly, a metaphor for life.
The journey is obstacled by moody waters and ships carrying people that wish you harm. But, along the way, you will encounter a chain of tropical islands, – safe havens open to discovery and exploration, and a temporary reprieve from the harsh environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Psilocybin</title>
      <link>/psilocybin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 06:00:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/psilocybin/</guid>
      <description>At the onset, It gently commanded me to lie down, as if my body was not meant to interfere in any way with Its function. With eyes shut, I swept through chrome waterfalls and past floating baroque-like structures that vibrated and pulsated with the rhythm of splashing water nearby. When I forced my eyes open I could see rainbow hexagons spinning and swirling instead of the usual dancing specks you see when you look at clear blue skies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I write code, prose, and (sometimes) academic papers.
Contact sphotavada@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
