<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>thoughts on sarpa hara ☾</title>
    <link>/tags/thoughts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in thoughts on sarpa hara ☾</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 06:00:35 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Psychiatry</title>
      <link>/psychiatry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 06:00:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/psychiatry/</guid>
      <description>Only psychiatrists will ask you if you want to go from dose X to dose Y of some given drug. Who should be doing the asking? If years of medical school are doing the asking, something is wrong.
Only psychiatrists will chastise you for giving the “wrong” response, because they weren’t asking you, they were giving you the illusion of free will by offering the opportunity to show alignment with their opinion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Parroting the Soundbites of Anti-Drug Propaganda</title>
      <link>/propaganda/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 19:11:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/propaganda/</guid>
      <description>I believe that the drug enthusiast community is becoming increasingly better at striking a behavioral balance between normalizing sustainable and responsible drug-fueled hedonism and making the idea of harm reduction salient.
Most of us have been exposed to biased, moralistic anti-drug propaganda. Some of us (rightfully so) aim to deconstruct such propaganda and invalidate it as a reductionist, uninformed viral idea about a specific drug (“GHB is a date-rape drug.&amp;quot;) or a category of substances (“All opioids are morbidly addictive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Metaphor for Life and Fun</title>
      <link>/metaphor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 15:00:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/metaphor/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Just have fun and enjoy life.&amp;rdquo;
Imagine that you have set out to discover a new continent. All the years behind you were spent dreaming of this achievement. Likely, you would be crossing vast bodies of water and weathering numerous storms. This journey is, expectedly, a metaphor for life.
The journey is obstacled by moody waters and ships carrying people that wish you harm. But, along the way, you will encounter a chain of tropical islands, – safe havens open to discovery and exploration, and a temporary reprieve from the harsh environment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
