<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on sarpa hara 𓆏</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on sarpa hara 𓆏</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 19:07:37 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mirogabalin [Besylate]</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/mirogabalin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 19:07:37 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/mirogabalin/</guid>
      <description>Gabapentinoids are the Vegemite™ of pharmaceuticals: it&amp;rsquo;s all love or hate, and almost never in between. If you clicked on this post, you are probably familiar with the fuzzy, electrifying stimulation brought about by an unholy dose of Pregabalin, or the fickle GHB-like lust from scarfing down Phenibut by the tablespoon, or the hassle of leaving CVS with bucket-sized refills of Gabapentin – the original gangsta Gabapentinoid.
I had assumed that my own first-hand familiarity with the &amp;lsquo;Noids made me well-equipped for my future acquaintance with Tarlige™ (Mirogabalin Besylate).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyclazodone</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/cyclazodone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 12:38:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/cyclazodone/</guid>
      <description>Have you heard about the new kid on the block? If you frequent r/researchchemicals, you might have.
&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Boring history lesson begins. &amp;lt;&amp;lt;&amp;lt;
The kid is not so new. In the late 60s and early 70s, pharmaceutical amphetamine abuse in the United States was hiking up a steep hill. The Benzedrine Era was nearing its end, making way for everyone&amp;rsquo;s favorite Cunt-Rolled Substances Act of 1971. For pharmaceutical manufacturers, it was research o&amp;rsquo;clock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phendimetrazine [Tartrate]</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/phendimetrazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 03:18:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/phendimetrazine/</guid>
      <description>I’ve had the fortune of running the stimulant gamut, from Adderall to Desoxyn. Going into this experience, I had some comparisons to draw. The literature on this compound was intriguing, but In my skeptical expectations there were no foreseeable surprises. It’s another stimulant, what’s the big dealio? Golly gee I was mistaken.
Didn’t even walk 50 feet from the pharmacy before popping one because I’m an impatient and excitable SOB. Walking to the subway on a chilly northeastern evening, I was hoping the 35mg of obscure stim goodness would warm me up a little.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gaboxadol [Hydrochloride]</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/gaboxadol/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 23:53:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/gaboxadol/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: I can&amp;rsquo;t and don&amp;rsquo;t recommend Gaboxadol to anyone because it is a narrowly studied substance, and everything I say is just my opinion and not medical advice.
Tonight we&amp;rsquo;re packing 20mg of Gaboxadol HCl in a gelatin cap in hopes of getting some stellar sleep, or I don&amp;rsquo;t know, a couple&#39; rotating cubes or whatever.
I&amp;rsquo;m cheating a little because this is technically my 2nd trial. The 1st &amp;ldquo;allergy&amp;rdquo; trial was done with 10mg down the hatch, about a week ago.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
